<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tommy Ho</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tommy Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:18:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Thinking</title>
      <link>/project/design-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:18:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/design-thinking/</guid>
      <description>My role on the team In the beginning, three members of the team each represent three different backgrounds of business, user experience, and technology, and I am the technology person considering my computer science background. Originally, I supposed myself would be like stopping my teammates from overly relying on technologies and telling them what&amp;rsquo;s impossible for the technology during the discussion. In the end, it turns out that I am the one overly relying on technical solutions since we keep refining our solutions based on the user research we have been conducted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARGAN</title>
      <link>/project/argan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:55:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/argan/</guid>
      <description>Image-to-image translation has been a popular topic since the Deep Learning had taken over a important position in research field regarding Computer Vision. In such kind of task, the model will usually learn a mapping G : X → Y such that the distribution of generated images from G(X) is indistinguishable from the distribution Y. What we have achieved in this project is having aids from additional image encoded with input, to assist the model find the mapping more easily to the desired output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Sarcasm Detection</title>
      <link>/project/twitter-sarcasm-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:54:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/twitter-sarcasm-detection/</guid>
      <description>Precise semantic presentation of a sentence and definitive information extraction are key steps in the accurate processing of sentence meaning, especially for figurative phenomena such as sarcasm, irony and metaphor. Semantic modeling faces a new challenge in social media because grammatical inaccuracy is commonplace yet many previous state-of-the-art methods exploit grammatical structure. For sarcasm detection over social media content, researchers so far have counted on Bag-of-Words, N-grams and etc. In this project, we apply a neural network semantic model for sarcasm detection on Twitter sarcasm dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>