<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Kuan-Wei Ho (Tommy Ho)</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Kuan-Wei Ho (Tommy Ho)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 17:22:31 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Storyteller</title>
      <link>/project/ai-storyteller/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 17:22:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ai-storyteller/</guid>
      <description>In this project, we design an AI model to generate believable Chinese stories based on MIT Media Lab&amp;rsquo;s ConceptNet semantic database. The project is seperated into two parts. The first part is to use Monte Carlo tree search to generate believable commonsense words sequence based on the semantic information provided by ConceptNet; the second part is to translate the sequence composed of commonsense Chinese words and relations into natural Chinese language sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARGAN</title>
      <link>/project/argan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:55:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/argan/</guid>
      <description>Image-to-image translation has been a popular topic since the Deep Learning had taken over a important position in research field regarding Computer Vision. In such kind of task, the model will usually learn a mapping G : X → Y such that the distribution of generated images from G(X) is indistinguishable from the distribution Y. What we have achieved in this project is having aids from additional image encoded with input, to assist the model find the mapping more easily to the desired output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Sarcasm Detection</title>
      <link>/project/twitter-sarcasm-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:54:46 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/twitter-sarcasm-detection/</guid>
      <description>Precise semantic presentation of a sentence and definitive information extraction are key steps in the accurate processing of sentence meaning, especially for figurative phenomena such as sarcasm, irony and metaphor. Semantic modeling faces a new challenge in social media because grammatical inaccuracy is commonplace yet many previous state-of-the-art methods exploit grammatical structure. For sarcasm detection over social media content, researchers so far have counted on Bag-of-Words, N-grams and etc. In this project, we apply a neural network semantic model for sarcasm detection on Twitter sarcasm dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>